♪ HOT SHH ♪
♪ MMMMMM ♪
♪ I'M GOIN DOWN DOWN BABY ♪
♪ YO' STREET IN A RANGE ROVER ♪
♪ BOOM, BOOM BABY,
LET IT GO LET IT GO ♪
♪ SHIMMY SHIMMY COCOA WHAT? ♪
♪ LISTEN TO IT POUND ♪
♪ LIGHT IT UP AND TAKE A
PUFF, PASS IT TO ME NOW ♪
♪ YOU CAN FIND ME, IN ST.
LOUIS ROLLIN' ON DUBS ♪
♪ SMOKIN' ON DUBS IN CLUBS,
BLOWIN' UP LIKE COCOA PUFFS ♪
♪ SIPPIN' BUD, GETTIN'
PERVED AND GETTING DUBBED ♪
♪ DAPS AND HUGS, MEAN
MUGS AND SHOULDER SHRUGS ♪
♪ AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE,
'CCUMULATED ENOUGH SCRATCH ♪
♪ JUST TO NAVIGATE IT,
WOOD DECORATED ON CHROME ♪
♪ AND IT'S CANDY
PAINTED, FANS FAINTED ♪
♪ WHILE I'M ENTERTAININ' ♪
♪ WILD AIN'T IT? HOW ME
AND MONEY END UP HANGIN' ♪
♪ I HANG WITH HANNIBAL
LECTOR (HOT SHH!) ♪
♪ SO FEEL ME WHEN I BRING IT ♪
♪ SING IT LOUD (WHAT?) ♪
♪ I'M FROM THE LOU
AND I'M PROUD ♪
♪ RUN A MILE - FOR THE CAUSE,
I'M RIGHTEOUS ABOVE THE LAW ♪
♪ PLAYA MY STYLE'S RAW, I'M
"BORN TO MACK" LIKE TODD SHAW ♪
♪ FORGET THE FAME,
AND THE GLAMOR ♪
♪ GIVE ME D'S WIT
A RUBBER HAMMER ♪
♪ MY GRAMMAR BE'S EBONICS,
GIN TONIC AND CHRONIC ♪
♪ SCRATCH BIONIC IT'S IRONIC,
SLAMMIN' HATERS LIKE ONYX ♪
♪ LUNATICS 'TIL THE DAY I DIE ♪
♪ I RUN MORE GAME THAN
THE BULLS AND SONICS ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' DOWN DOWN BABY,
YO' STREET IN A RANGE ROVER ♪
♪ BOOM, BOOM BABY,
LET IT GO, LET IT GO ♪
♪ SHIMMY SHIMMY COCOA
WHAT? LISTEN TO IT POUND ♪
♪ LIGHT IT UP AND TAKE A
PUFF, PASS IT TO ME NOW ♪
♪ I'M GOIN DOWN DOWN BABY,
YO' STREET IN A RANGE ROVER ♪
♪ BOOM, BOOM BABY,
LET IT GO, LET IT GO ♪
♪ SHIMMY SHIMMY COCOA
WHAT? LISTEN TO IT POUND ♪
♪ LIGHT IT UP AND TAKE A
PUFF, PASS IT TO ME NOW ♪
♪ WHO SAY PRETTY BOYS
CAN'T BE WILD, WILD ♪
♪ LOUD, O.K. CORRAL
AND JUST FOUL ♪
♪ AND JUST RUN IN THE CLUB
AND BUST IN THE CROWD ♪
♪ HOW ? ASK ME AGAIN
AND IT'S GOIN DOWN ♪
♪ NOW, COME TO THE CIRCUS
AND WATCH ME CLOWNIN' ♪
♪ POUNDIN' , WHAT YOU BE
GIVIN' WHEN I'M AROUND ? ♪
♪ FROWNIN' ♪
♪ TALKIN' THAT WHEN
I LEAVE THE TOWN ♪
♪ SAY NOW, CAN YOU
COME OUT TO PLAY NOW? ♪
♪ HEY I'M, READY TO CUT
YOU UP ANY DAY NOW ♪
♪ PLAY BY, MY RULES
BOO AND YOU GON' STAY ♪
♪ MAY I, ANSWER YO' THIRD
QUESTION LIKE A.I. ♪
♪ SAY HI, TO MY
LEFT IN THE SLAMMA ♪
♪ FROM ST. LOUIS TO MEMPHIS ♪
♪ FROM TEXAS BACK UP
TO INDIANA, CHI-TOWN ♪
♪ K.C. MOTOWN TO ALABAMA ♪
♪ L-A, NEW YORK
YANKEE TO HOTLANTA ♪
♪ 'OUISIANA, GETTING PAID
OFF AS "COUNTRY GRAMMAR" ♪
♪ SMOKIN' IN SAVANNAH ♪
♪ BLOW THIRTY MILL'
LIKE I'M HAMMER ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' DOWN DOWN BABY,
YO' STREET IN A RANGE ROVER ♪
♪ BOOM, BOOM BABY,
LET IT GO, LET IT GO ♪
♪ SHIMMY SHIMMY COCOA
WHAT? LISTEN TO IT POUND ♪
♪ LIGHT IT UP AND TAKE A
PUFF, PASS IT TO ME NOW ♪
♪ I'M GOIN DOWN DOWN BABY,
YO' STREET IN A RANGE ROVER ♪
♪ BOOM, BOOM BABY,
LET IT GO, LET IT GO ♪
♪ SHIMMY SHIMMY COCOA
WHAT? LISTEN TO IT POUND ♪
♪ LIGHT IT UP AND TAKE A
PUFF, PASS IT TO ME NOW ♪
♪ LET'S SHOW THESE GUYS HOW
TO MAKE THESE MILLI-ONS ♪
♪ SO YOU QUIT
ACTIN' SILLY, MON ♪
♪ KID QUICKER THAN BILLY, MON ♪
♪ TALKIN' REALLY
AND I NEED IT MON ♪
♪ FLOWS I KICK 'EM FREELY MON,
'SPECIALLY OFF REMI, MON ♪
♪ KEYS TO MY BEEMER, MON
HOLLA AT BEENIE MAN ♪
♪ SEE ME, MON, CHEIFIN
ROLLIN' DEEPER THAN ANY MON ♪
♪ THROUGH JENNINGS MON, THROUGH
U-CITY BACK UP TO KINGSLAND ♪
♪ WIT' NICE LETTERS,
SHEIST SLAYERS ♪
♪ WHO SNATCH YO' LIFE ♪
♪ TRIFE ♪
♪ WHO PRODUCE AND SELL THE
SAME BEAT TWICE ♪
♪ (HOT SHH!) ICE BABY, ALL
OVER CLOSE TO NEVER SOBER ♪
♪ FROM BROKE TO HAVIN' BRO-KERS
MY PRICE RANGE IS ROVER ♪
♪ NOW I'M KNOCKIN'
LIKE JEHOVAH ♪
♪ LET ME IN NOW, LET ME IN NOW ♪
♪ BILL GATES, DONALD
TRUMP LET ME IN NOW ♪
♪ SPIN NOW, I GOT MONEY
TO LEND MY FRIENDS NOW ♪
♪ WE IN NOW, CANDY BENZ,
KENWOOD AND 10"S NOW ♪
♪ I WIN NOW (WHOO!)
LESBIAN TWINS NOW ♪
♪ SEEIN' NOW, THROUGH THE
PEN I MAKE MY ENDS NOW ♪
♪ I'M GOIN DOWN DOWN BABY,
YO' STREET IN A RANGE ROVER ♪
♪ BOOM, BOOM BABY,
LET IT GO, LET IT GO ♪
♪ SHIMMY SHIMMY COCOA
WHAT? LISTEN TO IT POUND ♪
♪ LIGHT IT UP AND TAKE A
PUFF, PASS IT TO ME NOW ♪